Guide to the Stanford Alumni Photographs
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford alumni photographs
1942-1961
PC0057
Aten, Imogen.
0.75 Linear feet
Photographs, 1942-61, a few with notes, of Stanford students, their spouses, and their children. Many of the student pictures are of men and women in the military service during World War II.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Imogen Aten was accountant and office manager for the Associated Students of Stanford University.
Description of the Collection
Photographs, 1942-61, a few with notes, of Stanford students, their spouses, and their children. Many of the student pictures are of men and women in the military service during World War II.
Access Terms
Aten, Imogen.; Bing, Peter.; Cuthbertson, Kenneth.; Haffner, Robert Louis.; Haugh, James C.; Johannessen, Edward.; Steinbaum, Stanley.; Photoprints.
Collection Contents
- Photographs
  - Algar, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aten, Imogen (?), undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A, 1942, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Best, Bob, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bing, Peter, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ba-Bm, 1942, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bull, Charles & Family, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Burns, Jim, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Butner, Ted, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bo-Bz, 1931, 1941, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Clatworthy Children, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ca-Cl, 1930, 1954, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cobbs, John & Family, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cornell, Ted & Family, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cusick, Joe & kathy Moore, 1955, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cuthbertson, Ken & Family, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Co-Cz, 1933, 1935, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Denny, Gerorge V & Albert L., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - D, 1956, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - E, 1944, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Farguharson, Jim, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ferrari, Victor A., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Fontius, Charles H., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Forden, Jeannie Bobis & Family, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Frank, Dick & Family, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Freelen, Bob, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Freer, Larry, 1938, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - F, 1920, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Gable, Bob, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Grimes, John & Geroge & Children, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - G, 1941, 1944, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Haffner, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Hammett, Ray & Family, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Hammond-Children, 1954, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Haugh, James, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Havard, Bobby (Son of Ed Havard), 1954 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Hilleary, Charmian Kolai & Children, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Ha-Hi, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Ho, 1943, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Jessup, Bruce & Family, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Johannessen, Edward & Family, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - J, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Kennedy, Robert C, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Killefer, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Krupp, Lester, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - K, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Lanz, Henry & Family, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Leonard, Delight Kolar, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - L, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - McKenna, George & Family, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Mitguard, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Montalvo, Marty, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Mulvana-Children, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Myers, Bill & Family, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Ma, 1938, 1946, 1949, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Mc, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Me-Mi, 1943, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Mo, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - N-O-P, 1942, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - R, 1936, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 60)